Finding Aid for Arnold Gingrich Papers 1932-1975
Bentley Historical Library, University of Michigan
Arnold Gingrich Papers 1932-1975
Gingrich, Arnold.
85188 Aa/2
Founding editor of Esquire magazine; collection is a mix of personal papers and business records, biographical information, personal correspondence with or about many of the authors who contributed to the magazine, speeches and photographs.
24.5 linear feet
Bentley Historical Library University of Michigan
The collection was the gift of the Arnold Gingrich estate and came to the library in December 1976. Donor no. 5972
The collection is open for research.
Founding editor of Esquire Magazine in 1933 and its publisher beginning in 1952, Arnold Gingrich was a distinguished author, journalist, and nurturer of literary talent. Born in Grand Rapids, Michigan December 5, 1903, he graduated from the University of Michigan in 1925. He began his career writing advertising copy for a group of Chicago-based trade magazines. In 1931, he became the first editor of Apparel Arts (which later became Gentlemen's Quarterly). In 1933, along with David Smart, a publisher, and his partner William Weintraub, Gingrich helped to found Esquire, and where he given the title of editor and vice president. In 1936, he took on additional responsibilities as editor of Coronet. At Esquire, in its early years, Gingrich was responsible for attracting famous authors to write for the magazine. These included Ernest Hemingway, F. Scott Fitzgerald, John O'Hara, John Steinbeck, H.L. Mencken, and Sinclair Lewis. Published in later years were such authors as Vladimir Nabokov, John Updike, Saul Bellow, James Baldwin, and Truman Capote. He continued with all of these responsibility until 1945 when moved to Switzerland serving as European editor of Esquire and Coronet (1945-1949).
Gingrich returned to the United States in 1949 becoming vice president of Cowles Magazines, Inc. where he worked until 1951. In 1952 he was named publisher and senior vice president of Esquire. Here he was responsible for much of the magazine's renewed popularity in the 1950s, 60s, and 70s when the magazine became more journalistic in its content. Gingrich served in this responsibility until 1974 when he was named senior vice president and editor-in-chief of Esquire and Gentlemen's Quarterly.
In addition to his publishing responsibilities, Gingrich was a notable author of books and articles, many of them dealing with his passion for fly-fishing. Also as an avocation, Gingrich was a collector of old violins.
Gingrich died July 9, 1976.
The Gingrich collection which covers the period of 1932 to 1975 has been arranged into ten series: Biographical/personal; Authors - Special; Personal correspondence; Speeches/Symposia; Esquire Magazine Office Files; Arnold Gingrich Writing Projects; Organizational Affiliations; Fly-fishing; Sound Recordings; and Photographs.
The Gingrich papers consists of a mixture of personal and office files detailing the management of Esquire magazine and Gingrich's various other interests and activities. The collection, consisting of correspondence, speeches, photographs, and subject files, should be used in conjunction with the files of Esquire Magazine which came to the library at the same time but with a separate deed of gift. The two collections together are indispensable for any study of Esquire, Gingrich's career as a publisher, and the influence of Gingrich on the careers of some of America's most important literary figures of the twentieth century.
Subjects:
Authors, American.; Esquire, Inc.; Fishing.; Fly fishing.; Periodicals, Publishing of--New York (State)--New York.; Violin music.; Esquire (New York, N.Y.)
Subjects - Visual Material:
Boats.; Detroit River (Mich. and Ont.); Dwellings.; Gingrich, Arnold.; Gingrich family.; Musicians.; Studios and workshops.; University of Michigan--Alumni and alumnae.; Williams, G. Mennen, 1911-1988.
Contributors:
Armstrong, Louis, 1900-1971.; Bourjaily, Vance Nye.; Buchwald, Art.; Dos Passos, John, 1896-1970.; Engle, Paul, 1908-1991; Fitzgerald, F. Scott (Francis Scott), 1896-1940.; Gallico, Paul, 1897-1976; Helck, Peter, 1893-1988; Hemingway, Ernest, 1899-1961.; Hoff, Syd, 1912-2004; Huxley, Aldous, 1894-1963.; Knopf, Alfred A., 1892-1984.; Levin, Meyer, 1905-1981; MacDonald, Dwight.; Pegler, Westbrook, 1894-1969.; Rosten, Leo, 1908-1997; Seager, Allan, 1906-1968.; Stuart, Jesse, 1907-
Genre/Form:
DVDs.; Photographs.
- Biographical/personal
  The Biographical/personal series consists of clippings and biographical information collected about Gingrich as well as substantial materials relating to his family's genealogy. The Biographical/personal series consists of clippings and biographical information collected about Gingrich as well as substantial materials relating to his family's genealogy.
  - Biographical material
  - Genealogical material, 3 folders (Box 1)
  - Miscellanea (Box 1)
- Authors-Special
  The Authors - Special File consists of materials pulled together by Gingrich most probably because of their special meaning to him. These are his files on F. Scott Fitzgerald and Ernest Hemingway. The Fitzgerald files cover the years 1934 to 1939 and consist of telegrams, correspondence, and copies of the "Pat Hobb" stories that the author wrote for Esquire. Much of this material is photocopied. The Ernest Hemingway files date from 1933 to 1939 and include correspondence and typed drafts of articles written for Esquire, notably "The Snows of Kilimanjaro." Most of the correspondence is also photocopied, but the drafts of articles are original.
  - Fitzgerald, F. Scott (Box 1)
    - Telegrams 1934-1935 (Box 1)
    - Correspondence and "Pat Hobby" stories 1939, 4 folders (Box 1)
      (photocopies)
    - "Pasting it Together" 1936 (Box 1)
    - "Pat Hobby" tear sheets (Box 1)
  - Hemingway, Ernest
    - Correspondence with 1933-1939, 9 folders (Box 1)
    - Draft of "The Snows of Kilimanjaro" (Box 1)
    - Drafts of letter from Africa and other articles for Esquire Magazine, 4 folders (Box 1)
- Personal correspondence
  Personal Correspondence covers the period of 1932 to 1975 and is made up of two subseries: the first covering the years 1932 to 1950 is arranged chronologically, the second which is arranged alphabetically covers the period of 1951 to 1975. The letters in these files document Gingrich's many interests, apart from Esquire Magazine: violins and violin collecting, fishing, conservation, club memberships, and involvement with arts organizations. Because the magazine was so much a part of his life, this series obviously has importance to the study of Esquire and should be researched in conjunction with the Esquire Magazine Office File series (which follows) and the Esquire Magazine record group also on file at the library. Personal Correspondence covers the period of 1932 to 1975 and is made up of two subseries: the first covering the years 1932 to 1950 is arranged chronologically, the second which is arranged alphabetically covers the period of 1951 to 1975. The letters in these files document Gingrich's many interests, apart from Esquire Magazine: violins and violin collecting, fishing, conservation, club memberships, and involvement with arts organizations. Because the magazine was so much a part of his life, this series obviously has importance to the study of Esquire and should be researched in conjunction with the Esquire Magazine Office File series (which follows) and the Esquire Magazine record group also on file at the library.
  - 1932-1950 (Chronological File)
    - 1932-1944, 16 folders (Box 1)
    - 1945-1950, 13 folders (Box 2)
  - 1951-1975 (Alphabetical File)
    (includes some earlier dated papers)
    - A, 3 folders (Box 2)
      (include letter from Louis Armstrong)
    - American Cancer Society (Box 2)
    - Arazi, I. S. (Box 2)
    - B-Bz, 8 folders (Box 2)
    - Baer, Howard, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Barta, Frederick (Box 2)
    - Biays, Lalla (Box 2)
    - Big Bend Club (Box 2)
    - Bradford, Roark (Mrs.) (Box 2)
    - Brody, Iles (Box 2)
    - Bruccoli, Matthew, concerning Fitzgerald-Hemingway Annual, 2 folders (Box 2)
    - Buckler, Ernest, R (Box 2)
    - C-Cz, 4 folders (Box 2)
    - Cameron, Angus (Box 2)
    - Campbell, Elmer Simms, 5 folders (Box 2)
    - Cancer fund (Box 3)
    - Cason, Jessie M (Mrs. E.D.) (Box 3)
    - Chesnutt, Rosalie (Mrs. Omar) (Box 3)
    - Corner, Charles, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Copyright, Coalition for Fair (Box 3)
    - Crown Publishers (Box 3)
    - Curtis Publishing Company (Box 3)
    - D-Dz, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Deshotelle, Raymond (Box 3)
    - Deutsch, Hermann, 3 folders (Box 3)
    - Druian, Rafael, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Duff, Nell (Box 3)
    - Dunn, Ruth (Mrs. Robert), 2 folders (Box 3)
    - E-Ez (Box 3)
    - Estrada, Irene (Mrs. Luis) (Box 3)
    - Europe 1959 (Box 3)
      (includes schedules)
    - F-Fz, 2 folders (Box 3)
    - Feather, Leonard G (Box 3)
    - Field and Stream (Box 3)
    - Fishing (Box 3)
    - Fishing, Canadian (Box 3)
    - Fitzgerald, F. Scott
      - Correspondence concerning 1960-1973, 3 folders (Box 3)
      - Correspondence with Laura Guthrie Hearne concerning, 4 folders (Box 3)
    - Fitzgerald, Scottie (Box 3)
    - Fox, Charles and Gerald Foran, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Friedlander, Jules (Box 4)
    - G-Gz, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Gattis, Murrah, 4 folders (Box 4)
    - Gilliland, Hayes (Box 4)
    - Groth, John, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - H-Hz, 5 folders (Box 4)
    - Halle, Kay (Box 4)
    - Harrison, Thomas, concerning fishing (Box 4)
    - Hemingway, Ernest, correspondence concerning, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Henlein, Millard and Frankie (Box 4)
    - Henryville, Pa. (concerning fishing and conservation) (Box 4)
    - Holzer, Hans (Box 4)
    - I (Box 4)
    - J, 2 folders (Box 4)
    - Jennings, Mr. & Mrs. Preston (Box 4)
    - Jeter, R.G. (Box 4)
    - Johnson, Thurston (Box 4)
    - Jones, George R., 2 folders (Box 4)
    - K, 3 folders (Box 4)
    - Kahil, Dick (Box 5)
    - Karr, David (Box 5)
    - Kennedy, Scoop, concerning Society of Bacchus (Box 5)
    - Kerlee, Charles (Box 5)
    - Kerwin, Fred and Marjorie (Box 5)
    - Kessler, Mr. and Mrs. Hermann (Box 5)
    - Knopf, Alfred A., 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Kubie, Lawrence S. (Box 5)
    - Kuhns, Elinor C., 2 folders (Box 5)
    - L, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - Lawrenson, Helen Brown, 6 folders (Box 5)
    - Lawson-Johnston, John and Paulette (Box 5)
    - Loebe, Edward E (Box 5)
    - Lotos Club, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Luchs,Rev. Fred, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - M, 5 folders (Box 5)
    - Mc, 2 folders (Box 5)
    - McClane, A.J., 6 folders (Box 5)
    - Moennig, Willian,concerning violins, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - Myers, Walter, 3 folders (Box 5)
    - N, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Nathan, George and Julia (Box 6)
    - New York Public Library (fundraising) (Box 6)
    - Norm Thompson Outfitters, correspondence with Peter Alport, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - O, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - P-Q, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Peterson, Theodore, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Pfaelzer, M.A. (Box 6)
    - Ponall, Charles, 3 folders (Box 6)
    - R, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Reedy, Willia A. (Eastman Kodak) (Box 6)
    - Rembert Wurlitzer Inc., concerning violins (Box 6)
    - Renault, Louis (Box 6)
    - Rice, Robert L (Box 6)
    - Richards, Helene (Box 6)
    - Riess, Curt, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Ritz, Charles, 3 folders (Box 6)
      (correspondence concerning book about)
    - Robinson, Walter W (Box 6)
    - Roetter, Fritz (Box 6)
    - Rogowski, Theodore (Box 6)
    - Rosten, Leo (Box 6)
    - Sa-Sh, 4 folders (Box 6)
    - Si-Sz, 2 folders (Box 6)
    - Salmon, Richard (Box 6)
    - Samuelson, Arnold (Box 6)
    - Schwartz, Isaac Hillson (Box 6)
    - Schwiebert, Ernest (Box 6)
    - Shub, Harry, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Slaymaker, Samuel R., 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Smith,Carleton (Box 7)
      (correspondence with Roland Gelatt)
    - Snyder, Rowland, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Stinson, Robin Welch (Box 7)
    - T, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - U-V (Box 7)
    - Venables, Bernard, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Violins (offered for sale) (Box 7)
    - W, 4 folders (Box 7)
    - X-Y-Z (Box 7)
    - Walker, Arch and Arthur (Box 7)
    - Wechsberg, Joseph, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Wechsler, Abraham F. (Box 7)
    - Weintraut, William H. (Box 7)
    - Williams, Alfred Leslie, 2 folders (Box 7)
    - Winchester Press re books on angling (Box 7)
    - Wiswell, George and Dora (Box 7)
    - Wolfe, Henry (Box 7)
    - Woodford, Jack, 3 folders (Box 7)
    - Wulff, Lee (Box 7)
    - Young, Paul H. (Box 7)
- Speeches/Symposia
  Speeches/Symposia is a series of speeches given by Gingrich in the period of 1958 to 1975. Topics in this file are often recurring and include art and the business world, publishing, advertising, and customer tastes, fly-fishing, and freedom of expression. Also included here are files pertaining to Gingrich's participation in the Esquire Magazine symposium in the period 1958 to 1965.
  - Dated Speeches
    - 1958
      - Poor Richard Club, Philadelphia September 18, 1958 (Box 8)
        [8-1]
      - Advertising Club of Washington September 30, 1958 (Box 8)
        [8-2]
      - Chicago Federated Advertising Club October 22, 1958 (Box 8)
        [8-3]
    - 1959
      - "Moral Responsibilities of the Press." Institut Francais de Presse of the University of Paris April 24, 1959 (Box 8)
        [audio-tape in box 24]
        [8-4]
    - 1960
      - International Fashion Council, May 5, 1963. (Box 8)
        [8-5]
      - "The Maturing of American Taste" October 27, 1961 (Box 8)
      - Detroit Adcraft Club. (Box 8)
        [8-6]
    - 1962
      - "Magazines and the Culture Boom. Association of Publication Production Managers March 13, 1962 (Box 8)
        [8-7]
      - Maturing of American Taste. Botany-Daroff March 14, 1962 (Box 8)
        [8-8]
      - "The Uncommon Market". Poor Richard Club, Philadelphia, April 3,1962 (Box 8)
        [8-9]
      - "The Maturing of American Taste." Insurance Advertising Conference, Lido, Long Island June 25, 1962 (Box 8)
        [8-10]
      - "Today's Reading: A Reflection of American Taste." Medill School of Journalism, Northwestern University October 25, 1962, 2 folders (Box 8)
        [8-11; 8-12]
      - "The Uncommon Market of the Uncommon Man." Advertising Club of Louisville November 16, 1962 (Box 8)
        [8-13]
    - 1963
      - "Today"s New Customer." Cleveland Advertising Club January 29, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-14]
      - "Today's Customer." Los Angeles Advertising Club March 26, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-15]
      - "Today's Customer." Public Relations Society of America, San Francisco March 29, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-16]
      - "Today's Reading: A Reflection of American Taste." University of California, Berkeley March 28, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-17]
      - Papers concerning California speaking tour,March 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-18]
      - "Today's Reading: A Reflection of American Taste." University of Minnesota April 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-19]
      - Washington's Advertising Club May 28, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-20]
      - "The Facts of Life and Death in the Magazine World." Association for Education in Journalism, Lincoln,-Neb. August 28, 1963, 2 folders (Box 8)
        [8-21; 8-22]
      - Southern Methodist University, Dallas, Texas October 12, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-23]
      - Wayne State University, Detroit Michigan October 16, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-24]
      - "Today's Customer." Twin Cities Advertising Club October 24, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-25]
      - "Today's Reading: A Reflection of American Taste." Southern Industrial Editors Institute November 1, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-26]
      - Stanford University November 5, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-27]
      - "Today's Customer." Advertising Club, San Francisco November 6, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-28]
      - "New Consumer Demands and Motivation in an Affluent Society." American Marketing Association, Louisville, Ky. November 12, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-29]
      - "Today's Reading: A Reflection of American Taste." Twentieth Century Club, Cleveland, Ohio November 27, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-30]
      - Overseas Press Club, New York City January 9, 1963 (Box 8)
        [8-31]
    - 1964
      - "Today's Customer." Advertising Club of Des Moines January 14, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-32]
      - University of Texas May 7, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-33]
      - "Today's Customer." Advertising Club of Des Moines May 12, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-34]
      - University of Illinois School of Journalism May 13, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-35]
      - University of Colorado Telelecture May 19, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-36]
      - Grand Rapids Junior College June 12, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-37]
      - Georgetown Writers Conference, Washington, D.C. August 13, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-38]
      - "The Day the Editors Wrote Promotion." The Magazine Promotion Managers Association November 11, 1964 (Box 8)
        [8-39]
    - 1965
      - "Is Culture the Business of Business?" New York Board of Trade June 3, 1965, 2 folders (Box 8)
        [8-40; 8-41]
      - Brigham Young University Telelecture October 25, 1965 (Box 8)
        [8-42]
      - American Management Association Conference October 29, 1965 (Box 8)
        [8-43]
    - 1965
      - "Business and Culture." Public Relations Society of America November 23, 1965, 2 folders (Box 8)
        [8-44; 8-45]
    - 1966
      - New York Board of Trade: Business and the Arts Conference March 28, 1966 (Box 8)
        [8-46]
      - "Arts in the Board Room." Executives' Club, Chicago April 29, 1966, 2 folders (Box 8)
        [8-47; 8-48]
      - "Communicating with a Sophisticated Society. Western States Advertising Agencies Association, Inc. May 20, 1966 (Box 8)
        [8-49]
      - Creative Arts Conference, San Francisco, California May 21, 1966 (Box 9)
        [9-1]
    - 1967
      - George Polk Memorial Awards March 21, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-2]
      - Article for Arts Management Newsletter, March-April, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-3]
      - University of Michigan Sesquicentennial Conference on the Right of Free Expression March 2, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-4]
      - "The Partnership of Fly Fishing." Anglers' Club of Chicago April 4, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-5]
      - Festival of the Arts. National College of Education, Evanston, Ill. April 3-5, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-6]
      - Association for Womens' Committees for Symphony Orchestras April 26, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-7]
      - "Words will always count." Magazine Publishers Association, White Sulphur Springs, West Virginia June 3, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-8]
      - "10 Dares for the Writer." Writer's Digest Conference, University of Cincinnati, June 10, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-9]
      - Air Transportation Conference, Wings Conference June 28, 1967, 4 folders (Box 9)
        [9-10, etc.-9-13]
      - "The Dinosaur was the Biggest Thing Around. Magazine Industry Seminar, Harvard Business School July 31, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-14]
      - American Management Association: Business and Arts Conference October 2-4, 1967 (Box 9)
        [cancelled]
        [9-15]
      - American Society of Magazine Editors Seminar October 30, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-16]
      - Medaille Hoteliere Award November 21, 1967 (Box 9)
        [9-17]
    - 1968
      - Museum of Contemporary Art of Chicago January 22, 1968 (Box 9)
        [9-18]
      - Talk on Angling Literature. Flyfishers' Club of Harrisburg, Pa. April 5, 1968 (Box 9)
        [9-19]
      - Art Directors Club 13th Annual Communications Conference April 8-9, 1968 (Box 9)
        [9-20]
      - Business and Arts Conference, Bangor, Maine May 7, 1968 (Box 9)
        [9-21]
      - "Magazines at the Moment." Northwestern University Medill School of Journalism May 16, 1968, 2 folders (Box 9)
        [9-22; 9-23]
      - "Selling the Arts". American Symphony Orchestra League Conference June 3, 1968, 2 folders (Box 9)
        [9-24; 9-25]
      - "Salvaging the 20th Century" Esquire Seminar June 11, 1968, 4 folders (Box 9)
        [9-26, etc. 9-29]
      - "Unfinished Business." Henry Johnson Fisher Award September 17, 1968, 2 folders (Box 9)
        [9-30; 9-31]
      - Corporate Seminar, Saratoga Performing Arts Center October 4, 1968 (Box 9)
        [9-32]
      - "Communications Media, and People." Illinois-Library Association. Conference October 18, 1968 (Box 9)
        [9-33]
    - 1969
      - "Selling the Arts." Women's Committee of Chicago Symphony February 4, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-34]
      - National Music Council, New York City February 21, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-35]
      - American Management Association, New York City March 10, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-36]
      - Art Directors Club, New York City March 26, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-37]
      - "Culture and Its Institutions: Can They Keep Pace?" Oklahoma Library Association Conference April 24, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-38]
      - "Selling the Arts." Minnesota Orchestral Association May 1, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-39]
      - Woman's Club of Englewood Library Dedication May 2, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-40]
      - National Telephone Communications Conference May 23, 1969 (Box 9)
        [9-41]
      - "The Role of the Publisher in Terms of New Directions in Communications." 12th Annual International Marketing Promotion Conference May 27, 1969 (Box 10)
        [10-1]
      - Commencement Address. Manhattan School of Music June 3, 1969 (Box 10)
        [10-2]
      - Saint Paul Council of Arts and Sciences June 23, 1969 (Box 10)
        [10-3]
      - "The Coming Come Back of the Printed Word." 12th Annual Advertising Age Workshop, Chicago, Ill. July 31, 1969 (Box 10)
        [10-4]
      - Esquire Round Table Luncheon, Detroit, Mich. August 13, 1969 (Box 10)
        [10-5]
      - "Business and the Arts: the Ecology of Survival." Arts Award, New York Board of Trade September 18, 1969, 2 folders (Box 10)
        [10-6; 10-7]
      - "Historic Preservation and the Business Community." 23rd Annual Meeting, National Trust for Historic Preservation October 4, 1969 (Box 10)
        [10-8]
      - "Business and Youth." Publishers page, Esquire Magazine October 1969, 2 folders (Box 10)
        [10-9,10-10]
      - "What So Gladly You Teach." Annual Convention of National Guild of Community Music Schools, New York City November 10, 1969 (Box 10)
        [10-11]
    - 1970
      - Outstanding Consumer Magazine Executive Award, January 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-12]
      - "The Business End of the Arts." Avant-Garde Group of the Fort Lauderdale Museum of Art, Fort Lauderdale, Fla. January 8, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-13]
      - Palm Beach Round Table March 18, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-14]
      - "The Coming Comeback of the Printed Word. Advertising Council, Rochester, N.Y. April 1, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-15]
      - "The Business End of the Arts. Forum of the Oklahoma City Chamber of Commerce May 1, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-16]
      - "A Concern for Quality." Phi Beta Kappa Society, Oklahoma City May 1, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-17]
      - 21st Annual Dinner Meeting of the Arts Council, Winston-Salem, N.C. May 14, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-18]
      - "Business End of the Arts." 4th Annual Esquire-BCA awards May 21, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-19]
      - 6th Annual Meeting of the Seattle Opera Association June 2, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-20]
      - American Educational Theatre Conference August 25, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-21]
      - Symposium, Iowa State Arts Council, Davenport, Iowa October 23, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-22]
      - National Guild of Community Music Schools, Cleveland, Ohio November 9, 1970 (Box 10)
        [10-23]
    - 1971
      - Mannes College of Music, New York City March 4, 1971 (Box 10)
        [10-24]
      - Bridgeport Area Chamber of Commerce and Bridgeport Commission on the Arts September 27, 1971 (Box 10)